高维向量空间的大多数性质是非常不直观的。
themost of the properties of high dimensional vector spaces are very un intuitive.
它们不直观的一个方式是在高维向量空间中，
and one of the ways that they're un intuitive is in a high dimensional vector space,
一个词可以接近许多其他词
a word can be close to lots of other words
在不同的方向。
in different directions.
好吧，我们开始讨论我们是如何学习这些词向量的
okay sowe sort of started to talk about how we went about learning these word vectors i'm sort of gonna
花大约五分钟的时间进行优化，如果你想的话，这不是一个真正的优化类
take about a five minutedetour into optimization now this isn't really an optimization class if you want
学习很多关于优化的知识，在这里你可以学到更多关于优化的知识
to learn a lot about optimization where you can learn more about optimization if you do two twenty nine
如果你做一些像steven boys优化类的事情，你可以学到很多优化，但是
and if you do something like steven boys optimization class you can learn a lot of optimizationbut this
这是一个真正的婴儿优化，但只是为了确保每个人都在同一页
is sort of really baby optimization but just to make sure everyone's on the same page here
三张幻灯片对，最后我们做了什么，我很抱歉我写的东西
three slides right so what we did at the end what we did over there where i apologize that my writing
太小了，但这会给你一个机会，当你做作业二的时候，你必须写
was too smallbut that will give you the chance to when doing homework two and you have to write that
为了自己解决这个问题，并在过程中学习更多，所以我们得到的是成本函数
out to work it out for yourselves and learn more in the processright so what we had was the cost function
我们想要最小化，所以我们做的就是做一些微积分来计算梯度
that we wanted to minimize and so what we did was we did our bit of calculus to count calculate the gradient
关于我们的词向量的成本函数，它是我们的变量θ，然后我们
of the cost function with respect to our word vectors which were our variables theta and then what we
要做的就是说如果我们朝负的方向迈出一小步
want to do is say well if we take a small step in the direction of the negative of the gradient that
会把我们带到山下，在这个空间里，我们想继续这样做，然后朝着
will be taking us down down hill in this space and we wanna keep on doing that and sort of head to the
最小空间，我是说，当然，在我们的高维空间里，你知道这可能不太好
minimum of our space i mean of course in our high multidimensional space you know it might not be a nice
像这样平滑的曲线
smooth curve like this
可能是一条可怕的非凸曲线，但这只是个想法。
might be a horrible and non convex curve, but that's just the idea.
所以本质上，我们说我们有旧的参数。
so essentially, we say we've got the old parameters.
我们用公式求出目标函数的梯度。
we work out the gradient of the objective function using.